mailboxforwarding.com 2014-11-20

# Mailbox Forwarding - View Postal Mail Online, Mail Forwarding, Mailing Address, Virtual Office PO Box, and Private Mailbox Rental Services

Mailbox Forwarding will periodically review its privacy policy and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this policy at any time. Mailbox Forwarding considers the responsible use of personal information to be of vital importance. Mailbox Forwarding is committed to ensuring that to the best of our ability we meet all the requirements of the National Privacy Principals and the Privacy Act.

**Personal Information**

You can visit Mailbox Forwarding without revealing any personal information about yourself. However there are times when information will be collected, such as when signing up for our mailbox services. This information may include your name, home or business address, e-mail address and phone number. Personal information will only be collected when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. Unless we are ordered to do so by the U.S. postal service, a government agency, or a U.S. court, we will never share your personal information with anyone else.

**IP Addresses**

In general on Mailbox Forwarding websites, IP addresses (a number that is unique to the computer through which you are connected to the internet) are logged to track a user's session while the user remains anonymous. We analyse this data for certain trends and statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there.

When Mailbox Forwarding receives information about your session or about you, we only use it for research or to improve our site and the services we offer you.

**Cookies**

Mailbox Forwarding web pages use "cookies". Cookies can make your subsequent visits to the web page simpler and more seamless. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (However, by not accepting cookies, order and account pages will not display correctly). A server cannot find out a name or e-mail address, or anything about a user's computer, by using cookies.

**Communication**

By signing up for an account with Mailbox Forwarding, you consent to receiving email communications from us. These emails may include notices regarding your account (new mail items received, shipment sent, etc.) and other information related to our services, as well as periodic updates on new developments in our service or technology.

**Form 1583**

In regard to USPS Form 1583, which you must fill out by law after signing up for an account with Mailbox Forwarding, the USPS has enacted the following act:

> Your information will be used to authorize the delivery of your mail to the designated addressee as your agent. Collection is authorized by 39 USC 401, 403, and 404. Providing the information is voluntary, but if not provided, we cannot provide this service to you. We do not disclose your information without your consent to third parties, except for the following limited circumstances: to a congressional office on your behalf; to financial entities regarding financial transaction issues; to a USPS® auditor; to entities, including law enforcement, as required by law or in legal proceedings; to contractors and other entities aiding us to fulfill the service; and for the purpose of identifying an address as an address of an agent who receives mail on behalf of other persons. Information concerning an individual who has filed an appropriate protective court order with the postmaster will not be disclosed except pursuant to court order. For more information on our privacy policies, see our privacy link on usps.com®.

**Contact Us**

If you have further questions that this Privacy Policy did not address, please contact us.

|  |  | 

### First Month Free

Enter the promotional code **"freemonth"** during signup  
  
---
